First box goes in my car,
the other in the truck.
Guess that's it.
- You got everything?
- I think so.
I left the house keys and
the garage clicker by the nightstand.
Thanks.
So you still planning
to move in with your dad?
Just for a while.
- You gonna be okay?
- Me? Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I am gonna miss the cat.
You hate Sir Lancelot.
I did at first,
but over time I came to find...
Yeah, you're right, I hate that thing.
I put in a change of address
at the post office...
...but here's my address just in case.
I might be open to a trade.
I'll keep the cat, you take Alan.
Still got his carrier.
- Take care of yourself, Charlie.
- You do the same.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
Me too.
Well, she's gone.
You handled that very maturely.
What are you gonna do?
We tried, it didn't work. Life goes on.
You want a drink?
No, drinking isn't gonna
solve anything.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Really? Doesn't look like nothing.
Where you going?
Out for a swim.
You never go in the water.
That's because
I'm not a good swimmer.
- You don't think he's gonna...
- I don't know.
Charlie? Charlie, stop this!
Charlie, come back, it's not that bad!
Come on, Charlie,
you still got your family!
Very smart, now he's sprinting.
Damn it, Charlie, get out of that water!
We need to go after him.
Well, don't look at me.
I just ate, I gotta wait a half an hour.
I just washed my hair
and this is leave-in conditioner.
- What about Jake?
- At his mother's.
- Maybe we should give him a call.
- There's no time.
Water's really cold.
Just so you know,
we were about to come get you.
Charlie?
You awake?
Come on, man, it's time to get up.
Charlie?
- What?
- Aah!
I didn't see you there.
She was the best thing
that ever happened to me, Alan.
I understand,
but you've been up here for two days.
It's time to move on with your life.
There's no life to move on with.
Well, sure there is.
You've got money, a beautiful home,
good looks, all your hair...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have all the things you don't.
That wasn't really the point
I was trying to make, but, uh...
Come on.
- Where are we going?
- We are going to get you cleaned up.
No. No, I can't go in there.
It reminds me too much of Chelsea.
The bathroom?
That's where she used to brush her hair
and floss her teeth...
...and tinkle like a princess.
Okay, well,
where have you been tinkling?
I may need a new ficus.
I'm glad you came with me.
You needed to get out of the house.
No, what I need is to be loved again.
Uh, well, I think a good first step
is to stop urinating in the potted plants.
Jake, your dad's here.
Charlie, I was so sorry
to hear about you and Chelsea.
Thank you.
I know that breakups
can be very difficult.
Unless you're kicking out
your husband of 12 years.
That seemed remarkably easy.
It was.
You know the part
that I don't understand, Judith...
...is how somebody can tell you
they love you one day...
...then turn around
and break your heart the next.
Well, relationships are complicated.
People drift apart.
- Nobody's to blame.
- You blamed me.
It was your fault.
I tried to change, tried to become
the man she wanted me to be...
...but it wasn't enough.
Oh, I'm sure there's a part of her
that still loves you very much.
There a part of you that still loves me?
No.
What's wrong with him?
Your uncle's very upset
about his breakup.
Oh, yeah, that sucks.
Can I drive?
- Sure.
- Cool.
Let's go, crybaby.
Hi.
Yeah, hey, kind of busy here.
I can see that.
- Hi, I'm Jake's Uncle Charlie.
- Nicole.
What's the deal, Nicole,
are you tutoring our little genius here?
No, we're dating.
- Oh. Dating?
- Uncle Charlie?
Hang on.
Listen, Nicole, I love this kid
and I don't wanna see him get hurt.
- I'm not gonna hurt him.
- Oh, really?
You like him the way he is?
You don't wanna change him?
- Uncle Charlie...
- I got your back here, buddy.
Because let me tell you something.
This, here, is a lump of clay.
You know what it's gonna
be five, 10, 20 years from now?
A larger, more bitter lump of clay.
- Come on, let's go.
- Whoa, whoa.
Whoa, I'm not done.
If you're gonna dump him,
dump him now.
Don't wait till he falls in love, asks you
to marry him and have his children.
Okay, enjoy yourselves.
Are you out of your mind?
I mean well.
- Maybe it's time to go to your shrink.
- She's another woman...
...that wants to change me.
- You have to do something.
No. No.
If I can't have Chelsea,
I don't wanna live.
- Where you going?
- Strip club.
Ah, yes, death by lap dance.
Hey, Lord, it's Charlie.
I know it seems like I only call on you
when my ass is on fire.
But, well, let's face it,
that's how you made me.
Anyway, I'm just hurting
real bad since Chelsea left...
...and I was kind of hoping
that maybe you could...
...take away some of that pain.
Even with the help of your blessed wine,
I can't get through the day.
Even your blessed vodka's
stopped working.
So anything you can do
would be much appreciated.
Hey.
You got a light?
I like a little buzz before I pray.
Gets me closer to God.
Thanks.
Come on, Charlie, answer the phone.
Oh, damn it, voicemail.
Uh, Charlie, it's me again.
It has been three days.
Please call
and let us know you're okay.
- I think we should call the police.
- No, he'll turn up.
May be broke and riddled
with gonorrhea...
...but he'll find his way home.
No, I don't think
this is a typical bender.
He really cared for Chelsea.
You know, he put her in his will.
Anything happens to him,
she gets everything.
Really? So like if he swam out
in the ocean...
...and drowned, for instance,
she gets the house?
The house, the Mercedes,
the bank accounts, the music royalties.
Man, I just can't catch a break.
Hey, look what someone threw away.
Put that back outside.
And wash your hands.
Welcome to your new home, baby.
Hey, everybody.
I want you to meet the love of my life,
Mrs. Charlie Harper.
Better put me down.
I'm not wearing panties.
I told you he'd come home
with gonorrhea.
All right, who's who?
Well, this is my brother Alan.
Alan, Betsy.
Hello, brother.
- Call me Alan.
- Okay.
He doesn't look like such a mooch.
Okay, well, this is my mom, Evelyn...
...and she doesn't look
like such an Antichrist.
Hi, Mom.
Call me Mrs. Harper.
- This is my housekeeper, Berta.
- Don't call me at all.
And lastly, this is Jake.
Oh, are you my son?
I'll be whatever you want me to be.
- Actually, he's my son.
- Butt out, Dad.
Well, you've met everybody.
Why don't we go upstairs
and continue the honeymoon?
- We have got an upstairs?
Yep.
Are there people up here too?
I like her.
- Hey, Dad?
- Mm-hm.
Do I call Uncle Charlie's new wife
Betsy or Aunt Betsy?
I guess either one's okay.
- I'm gonna go with Aunt Betsy.
- Fine.
Aunt Betsy made
a lot of noise last night.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, she did.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm not complaining.
Good morning, family.
Morning.
- How we doing today?
- Good.
Will Aunt Betsy be joining us
or is she taking a hot, soapy shower?
She'll be right down.
So based on
this latest turn of events...
...would it be fair to say
you're over Chelsea?
Oh, absolutely.
Betsy and I are soul mates.
Soul mates? Uh-huh.
- So, where'd you meet your soul mate?
- Guess.
- Strip club?
- Wrong.
- Massage parlor?
Okay, I give up.
Betsy and I met in church.
So, what, she's a nun?
No, she's a stripper
and part-time masseuse.
See, I drove to the strip club,
but the parking lot was full...
...so I circled the block
looking for a spot...
...and found one right in front
of this little church.
For some reason, I don't know why,
I got out of my car...
...walked into church, started praying.
- Are you saying God sent you Betsy?
- I think he did.
Oh, Dad, we gotta get our asses
to church.
Then when I'm done,
I get up to leave...
...and she appears in front of me
like some kind of vanilla-scented angel.
Mm, vanilla.
So we get to talking, turns out she's
going through a difficult time as well.
Next thing, we're cleaning out her locker
at the club and driving to Vegas.
Where you got married.
I understand your skepticism,
but I'm telling you, this girl is special.
She's really sweet and spiritual.
Charlie?
- In here, baby.
Good news, bad news.
I got my period.
Oh, that's okay. We can take a break.
We don't have to.
There's more than one way
to skin a cat.
Oh, you are so wonderful.
- What are the other ways?
- Shh. Uh...
Can I talk to you in private
for a minute?
Sure. Bets, coffee's right there.
- You just make yourself at home.
- Okay.
- Morning, son.
- Morning, Mom.
I was gonna do a little topless
sunbathing, you're welcome to join me.
Okay, not to put too fine a point on it,
but you're out of your mind.
You need to call a lawyer and get
this marriage annulled immediately.
- I knew you wouldn't understand.
- Oh, I understand.
I understand you're still reeling
from losing Chelsea...
...and you're trying to fill the void
with a menstruating pole dancer.
Hey, hey, that's my wife
you're talking about.
You don't know anything about her.
I know I love her and she loves me
for exactly who I am.
- She doesn't want to change me.
- Oh, stop it.
Okay, you get one of those.
Next time, that hand comes back
a bloody stump.
- Charlie, please, I'm begging you.
- No. I'm doing the right thing.
You're lucky you're not a girl.
Having a hoochie
is like owning a vintage car.
Lot of maintenance and once a month,
you gotta put down an oil pan.
Okay, I may have made a mistake.
Chelsea?
Hey, Charlie.
What are you doing here?
- I need to see your daughter.
- I'm sorry, she's not here.
- Hi, Charlie. What's going on?
- Ed.
- Know when she'll be back?
- I'm not sure.
She took Skipper for a walk.
You're welcome to come in and wait.
Thank you.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just trying to be polite.
Did you consider that maybe
she doesn't want to see him?
Watch your tone, mister.
Sit, please.
Sorry the place is a mess,
we're still decorating.
I'm decorating, he's critiquing.
What? I can have opinions.
He wants me to just shut up
and be pretty.
So listen, I'm sorry things
didn't pan out with you and Chels.
Yeah, me too.
Relationships can be a lot of work.
Even if you've known someone
for 40 years.
That's right.
People get set
in their pigheaded ways.
You wanna get something
off your chest? Hm?
I'm right here.
You really wanna open
this kettle of fish now?
Oh, yeah, let's open it. Open it up.
Okay.
I'm just saying that two grown men
should be able to pick out a club chair...
...without it turning
into lwo-freaking-Jima.
Well, I'm not the one that thinks
that everything he sets his ass on...
...has to be made out of leather.
Lucky for you.
Come on, Skipper.
- Charlie.
- I'm sorry to drop in like this.
I just really needed to see you.
Okay. What's going on?
- Uh, well...
- Why don't we go...
...and leave these two alone?
Fine. Fine.
There's no law that says we can't order
the rug later and get two club chairs.
You see, right there.
That's why I love you.
What are you doing here?
Okay, well...
...I don't know how to say this
except just to say it.
I still love you very much
and I miss you like crazy.
I miss you too, Charlie.
Then what are we doing?
Taking time to figure out
if we're meant to be together.
And how the hell
are we supposed to do that?
I don't know. I guess
we should start dating other people.
What?
I'm not ready to see other people.
I don't know that I am either,
but we have to try.
Chelsea, I can't even think
about dating right now.
Can I tell you something
I've learned since we split up?
Sure. But first, marry me.
- No.
- Okay, just checking.
Probably some
legal complications anyway.
- What?
- Nothing. Nothing. Go ahead.
I learned that I shouldn't have
tried to change you.
You need someone
who loves you for you.
No, no, no. I need to be changed.
There's something seriously wrong
with me.
Please, Chelsea, take me back
and turn me into someone else.
- Wasn't a very good argument, was it?
- Nope.
Well, that's the best I got.
Okay. I guess I should get going.
I'm really sorry.
That's all right.
Say goodbye to your dad and Ed
for me.
I will.
They're a really cute couple.
I guess. It's a little weird for me.
Well, sure, you're probably used to
seeing your dad with your mom...
...and not a big, handsome black guy.
He is handsome.
Hey, Chels...
...I just want you to know
that if by chance...
...you should do something
crazy and stupid...
...like running off
and marrying some stranger...
...I would forgive you
and take you back with open arms.
- Good to know.
- Seriously.
I wouldn't hold it against you at all.
Thank you.
All right then.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Stop it, Ed, your beard tickles.
Come on, Skipper,
time for another walk.
- Uh, Charlie, we've got a little problem.
- What's up?
This is Betsy's husband.
Hello.
- Wanna catch me up?
- Really?
Calling him "Betsy's husband"
didn't do the trick?
She never said anything
about being married.
She never does.
- This has happened before?
- Oh, yes.
Any time I find her ring
inside her diaphragm case...
...I know she's off
on one of her little adventures.
- I don't believe this.
- Why do you put up with it?
Look at me.
I'd rather share a girl like Betsy...
...than have an exclusive relationship
with a box of porn magazines.
I hear you. That would be sad.
- Hey, baby.
Hey.
Charlie, I'm really sorry.
I was less than honest with you.
Sure. Let's call it "less than honest."
I did enjoy our honeymoon.
Me too.
Ha, ha. We stayed at Bellagio.
Nice.
Oh, we should go.
- Bye.
I'll make it up to you in the car.
Oh, Betsy,
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
How about that?
I guess I'm not married.
I guess not.
You know what that means.
Going back to church?
That means I just got three days
of unbelievable sex...
...with no obligations
and no commitment.
Please don't make me slap you again.
No, go ahead.
I think I got one more coming.
That's all right.
I'm happy that things worked out
for you.
Again.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, did I tell you
I won 18 grand in Vegas?
Ouch.